# **Atlant Syla**

### Designer

Pristina, Kosovo 10000 (+383) 049 480 532 info@myidea.design

#### **SUMMARY**

#### Personality

Passionate and innovative designer with a unique mix of creativity in design of multimedia marketing and campaigns, branding design, graphic design, visual conceptualization, illustration, user interface and experience design, proven by 5+ years of experience. Equipped with the ability to scalate brand awareness, overcome objections, staying in line with the clients requests and finishing deadlines in time. Always looking to learn something new.

**EXPERIENCE** 

Remote

#### Freelancer, Graphic Designer

Mar 2017 - Present

- · Collaborated with local and national clients, editors, department directors, supervisors also worked in different freelancing websites and marketing departments.
- Gained a lot of proffesional skills by designing illustrations, information graphics, edited photos, video editing, produced product catalogs, marketing materials such as brochures and flyers also designed client branding strategies, including logos, letterhead, brochures, environmental graphics and signage.

Remote

# Alavisuals, Senior Graphic Designer

Feb 2022 - Jan 2023

• Designed graphic content, illustrations and infographics. Ensured brand consistency throughout various social marketing projects. Refined images, fonts, layouts using graphic design softwares.

Pristina,KS

## OutKos, UI/UX Designer

May 2021 - Feb 2022

• Designed and tested UI elements and tools such as navigation menus, search boxes, CTAs, banners, layouts, page designs and links for landing pages. Producing UX design solutions through wireframes, storyboards, site maps, and prototypes.

Prisitna, KS

#### WhiteSpace, Video Editor

Jun 2020 - Jan 2021

• Conducted the recording and editing of audio and video content. Prepared storyboards edited video and audio and produced program videos. Checked edited videos and films for mistakes and made corrections when needed.

**EDUCATION** 

Prisitna, KS

#### **UBT** (University for Bussines and Technology)

Sep 2018 - Present

Computer Science and Engineering

• Studied about computer systems and networks, security, database systems, human computer interaction, vision and graphics, numerical analysis and programming languages. Now I'm specializing in Computer Graphics and Multimedia.

#### **CERTIFICATION**

# Jungle, Video Editor 3 months / Pristina, KS Roi Academy, Graphic Designer 2 months / Remote Com-ing, Basic of Programming 2 months / Pristina, KS Digital World, IT Essentials 3 months / Pristina, KS

#### **SKILLS**

•	Adobe Illustrator	•	Sketch

Adobe Photoshop
 Adobe Lightroom

• Adobe XD • Adobe After Effect

Adobe Premiere ProHTML / CSSAdobe IndesignFigma